supergift-giveaway.com 2008-01-25

# SuperGift-Giveaway.com

  |  |  |   
---|---  
  
|  |   
---  
|    
---  
  
Thank you for visiting the privacy policy page SuperGift-Giveaway.com the "Site". SuperGift-Giveaway.com takes privacy seriously, and wants you to feel comfortable using the Site. This page describes our online privacy policy ("Privacy Policy"). By visiting the Site, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy, as well as our terms of use. By applying for promotional offers, providing information to us, or otherwise using the Site in any way, you are further indicating your acceptance of this Privacy Policy and our terms of use. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy or our terms of use, please do not use or visit this Site, and do not disclose any information to us. This Privacy Policy does not apply to other online or offline SuperGift-Giveaway.com sites, products or services. 

**Changes to Privacy Policy**  
If we change this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by posting the revised privacy policy on the Site. It is your responsibility to periodically revisit the Site. We may also notify you by sending you an email notification to the email address that you provided to us. It is your responsibility to provide us with your current email address. If we revise our Privacy Policy to broaden our use of your personal information, you may contact us at the address below to request that we either refrain from using your personal information or destroy your personal information. 

**Collection of Personal Information**  
Each time you provide information to take advantage of a promotional offer, enter to win a contest, send us an email, or otherwise transmit information via the Site, SuperGift-Giveaway.com may obtain and collect personally identifiable information including (but not limited to) your name, email address, mailing address, and telephone number. You may also provide us with information that, when combined with personally identifiable information, provides us with a better idea of who you are, such as your gender, birthday, marital status, and education level (collectively with the personally identifiable information, "personal information"). If you choose to use our services, we may require you to provide information as indicated on the forms throughout the Site. 

Use of Personal Information   
SuperGift-Giveaway.com may always use and share with others your personal information: 

  * to enable us to generally respond to you, or to process, validate and verify requests and/or purchase orders; 
  * to fulfill any of your requests; 
  * to send information to you about additional goods or services; 
  * to compile and/or distribute information about our website users and usage patterns; 
  * to provide useful information to our website designers for developing new features and services; 
  * to tailor your experience on our websites, e.g., showing content that we believe may interest you or altering the content based on your personal preferences; and in any way we deem advisable to provide better goods or services to our customers. 

SuperGift-Giveaway.com may also use personal information for any marketing and survey purpose on behalf of itself and its affiliates and subsidiaries. SuperGift-Giveaway.com may disclose personal information to third party agents and independent contractors that help us conduct our marketing and survey efforts. Further, SuperGift-Giveaway.com may disclose personal information to other companies in connection with marketing efforts including but not limited to direct marketing, which may have no relationship to SuperGift-Giveaway.com. Finally, if SuperGift-Giveaway.com or any of its assets are acquired by or merged with another entity, member information will be one of the transferred assets. 

Additionally, SuperGift-Giveaway.com will use or disclose your personal information under the following circumstances: (1) in response to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; (2) in the event you violate or breach an agreement with SuperGift-Giveaway.com; (3) we believe you will harm the property or rights of SuperGift-Giveaway.com or those of SuperGift-Giveaway.com 's other customers, (4) we believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of SuperGift-Giveaway.com 's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law, or (5) personal information may also be shared with or sold to any successor to, or purchaser of, part or all of the assets of SuperGift-Giveaway.com. 

Opting-Out   
SuperGift-Giveaway.com members are automatically opted-in to receive SuperGift-Giveaway.com newsletters and offer e-mails at the time of enrollment. You may opt-out by visiting the unsubscribe page. 

Canceling Membership   
You may cancel your SuperGift-Giveaway.com membership at any time by visiting the unsubscribe page. If you decide to cancel your membership and later wish to re-enroll, you will not receive credit gifts earned using your previous account. SuperGift-Giveaway.com reserves the right to terminate or suspend any account at any time with or without notice. SuperGift-Giveaway.com does not tolerate any abuse, harassment, or fraudulent activity aimed towards other members or SuperGift-Giveaway.com. 

Cookies   
"Cookies" are a feature on your browser software. If enabled, cookies may store small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to any of this Site. Cookies assist us in tracking which of our features appeal the most to you and what content you may have viewed on past visits. When you visit this Site again, cookies can enable us to customize our content according to your preferences. We may use cookies to: keep track of the number of return visits to this Site; accumulate and report aggregate, statistical information on website usage; deliver specific content to you based on your interests or past viewing history; save your password for ease of access to our Site. You can disable cookies, although the Site may not function properly for you. Your browser preferences can be modified to accept or reject all cookies, or request a notification when a cookie is set. 

IP Addresses   
We automatically track certain information based upon your behavior on the Site. We may use this information to do internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behavior to better understand, protect and serve you and our community. This information may include the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on the Site or not), which URL you next go to (whether this URL is on the Site or not), your computer browser information, and your IP address. Your Internet Protocol ("IP") is a unique Internet "address" which is assigned to you by your Internet Service Provider ("ISP"). For local area network ("LAN"), DSL, or cable modem users, an IP address may be permanently assigned to a particular computer. IP addresses are automatically logged by Web servers, collecting information about a user's traffic patterns. While the IP address does not identify an individual by name, it may, with the cooperation of the ISP, be used to locate and identify an individual using the Web. Your IP address can, however, reveal what geographic area you are connecting from, or which ISP you are using. Finally, other websites you visit have IP addresses, and we may collect the IP addresses of those websites and their pages. 

Computer Profiles   
SuperGift-Giveaway.com may also collect and accumulate other anonymous data which will help us understand and analyze the Internet experience of our visitors. For instance, SuperGift-Giveaway.com may accumulate visitor data relating to referring domain names, the type of browsers used, operating system software, screen resolutions, color capabilities, browser plug-ins, language settings, cookie preferences, search engine keywords and JavaScript enablement. Unless you provide us with personally identifiable information, we will not use such visitor data to identify you. 

Links and Companies providing Offers   
This Privacy Policy applies only to the Site. The Site contains links that direct you to websites owned and operated by other companies. In particular, when you take advantage of a promotional offer, you will be directed to the web sites of our marketing partners that will also collect your personal information, such as credit card companies. SuperGift-Giveaway.com does not control, and assumes no responsibility for, the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third party websites, which may employ cookies and/or collect personal information. In addition, SuperGift-Giveaway.com will not and cannot censor or edit the content of any third party site. Please be sure to read the privacy policy of each third party website that you visit. 

Adult Supervision   
Persons under the age of 18 are not eligible to use this Site unsupervised and we ask that minors do not submit any personal information to us. Persons under the age of 18 may only use this Site in conjunction with and under the supervision of their parents or guardians. 

SuperGift-Giveaway.com does not knowingly collect contact or personal information from persons under the age of 13. This Site is not intended to solicit information of any kind from children under the age of 13. It is possible that by fraud or deception we may receive information pertaining to children under the age of 13. 

Location of Data and Security   
Your information may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which SuperGift-Giveaway.com or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using this Site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. 

We use procedural and technical safeguards to protect your personal information against loss or theft as well as unauthorized access and disclosure to protect your privacy, including encryption, and "firewalls." We employ many different security techniques to protect such data from unauthorized access by users inside and outside the company. However, perfect security does not exist on the Internet. 

Version 20070927 Effective Date:September 27, 2007  

|   
---  
  
Copyright © 2007 SuperGift-Giveaway.com All Rights Reserved.  
  
*This promotion is conducted exclusively by SuperGift-Giveaway.com, and is subject to participation terms and conditions. Receipt of your item requires compliance with offer terms, including: age and residency requirements; registration with valid e-mail address, shipping address and phone number; completion of user survey and sponsor offers. Upon completion of all requirements, we will ship your incentive gift to your verified shipping address. Fulfillment may be delayed based on availability. 

Trademarks, service marks, logos, and/or domain names (including, without limitation, the individual names of products and companies) are the property of their respective owners, who have no association with and do not make any endorsement of the products or services provided by SuperGift-Giveaway.com.
